A Guide to the Martha Baird Rockefeller Fund for Music records FA1420
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1957-1983; 2; 46.33 Cubic Feet 122 letter document boxes. Boxes 156-277.
  - Q-R-S-T-U-V
    - Richardone, Michael (Box 249, Folder 20)
    - Richards, Eric (Box 249, Folder 21)
    - Richards, Mr. Leslie (Box 249, Folder 22)
    - Richman, Mark (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Richter, Marga (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - Rife, Jean (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Riggs, Kathleen (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - Riis, Thomas L. (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Riley, Dennis (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - RILM Abstracts of Music Literature (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - Ringo, Jennifer (Box 250, Folder 8)
    - Roads, Curtis (Box 250, Folder 9)
    - Roark, Linda (Box 250, Folder 10)
    - Roberts, Rebecca (Box 250, Folder 11)
    - Roberts, Susan (Box 250, Folder 12)
    - Robin, Donna (Box 250, Folder 13)
    - Robinson, Laura English (Box 250, Folder 14)
    - Robinson, Sharon (Box 250, Folder 15)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 250, Folder 16)
    - Rockefeller Family Fund, 1969 (Box 250, Folder 17)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1964-1982 (Box 250, Folder 18)
    - Martha Baird Rockefeller - General Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 250, Folder 19)
    - Martha Baird Rockefeller - Personal Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 251, Folder 1)
    - Rockefeller, John D. 3rd (Box 251, Folder 2)
    - Rodriguez, Robert Xavier (Box 251, Folder 3)
    - Rogers, Carol (Box 251, Folder 4)
    - Rohr, Deborah (Box 251, Folder 5)
    - Rolandi, Gianna (Box 251, Folder 6)
    - Rolnick, Neil (Box 251, Folder 7)
    - Roloff, Roger (Box 251, Folder 8)
    - Rolufs, Linda (Box 251, Folder 9)
    - Ronish, Martha (Box 251, Folder 10)
    - Root, Michael (Box 251, Folder 11)
    - Rose, Andrea (Box 251, Folder 12)
    - Rosen, Jacqueline (Box 251, Folder 13)
    - Rosen, Nathaniel (Box 251, Folder 14)
    - Rosenblum, Mathew (Box 251, Folder 15)
    - Rosenthal, David (Box 251, Folder 16)
    - Rosenzweig, Michael (Box 251, Folder 17)
    - Ross, Elise (Box 251, Folder 18)
    - Ross, Eric (Box 251, Folder 19)
    - Ross, Francine (Box 251, Folder 20)
    - Ross, Pamela (Box 251, Folder 21)
    - Ross, Walter (Box 251, Folder 22)
    - Rosenfeld, Judith (Box 251, Folder 23)
    - Rossiter, David (Box 251, Folder 24)
    - Rothenburg, Sanford (Box 251, Folder 25)
    - Rothfuss, Earl Levering (Box 251, Folder 26)
    - Roulette (Box 251, Folder 27)
    - Rouse, Christopher (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Rouse, Mikel J. (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Roussakis, Nicolas (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Rova Saxophone Quartet (Box 252, Folder 4)
    - Rowley, Eugene (Box 252, Folder 5)
    - Rubinstein, David (Box 252, Folder 6)
    - Ruble, Mr. Leslie (Box 252, Folder 7)
    - Ruggles, Sandra (Box 252, Folder 8)
    - Rush, Celeste (Box 252, Folder 9)
    - Rush, Mr. Loren (Box 252, Folder 10)
    - Russell, Craig Henry (Box 252, Folder 11)
    - Russo, John (Box 252, Folder 12)
    - Rust, Rebecca (Box 252, Folder 13)
    - Ryerson, Greg (Box 252, Folder 14)
    - Rzewski, Frederic (Box 252, Folder 15)
    - Association of Professional Vocal Ensembles (APVE) - Conference, 1981 June 3-7 (Box 252, Folder 16)
    - Sabbeth, Alex (Box 252, Folder 17)
    - Sackett, John (Box 252, Folder 18)
    - St. John, Kathleen (Box 252, Folder 19)
    - St. Louis Symphony Orchestra (Box 253, Folder 1)
    - St. Luke's Chamber Ensemble (Box 253, Folder 2)
    - Salas, Jacqueline (Box 253, Folder 3)
    - Salas, Veronica (Box 253, Folder 4)
    - Salerno, Anna (Box 253, Folder 5)
    - Salzman, Eric (Box 253, Folder 6)
    - Sampen, John (Box 253, Folder 7)
    - Sampson, David (Box 253, Folder 8)
    - Samuel, Eugenia Hamilton (Box 253, Folder 9)
    - Sanabria, Pamela (Box 253, Folder 10)
    - San Diego Opera (Box 253, Folder 11)
    - Sandor, John (Box 253, Folder 12)
    - Sanford, Edward Clark, 1966-1978 (Box 253, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco Contemporary Music Players (Box 253, Folder 14)
    - San Francisco Opera Center, 1981-1982 (Box 253, Folder 15)
    - Sapieyeveski, Jerzy (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - Sapp, Allen (Box 254, Folder 2)
    - Sarbu, Eugene (Box 254, Folder 3)
    - Saragoza, Justin (Box 254, Folder 4)
    - Saucedo, Victor (Box 254, Folder 5)
    - Sauler, Gayna (Box 254, Folder 6)
    - Saylor, Bruce (Box 254, Folder 7)
    - Saylor, Roger W. (Box 254, Folder 8)
    - Scanlon, Pamela (Box 254, Folder 9)
    - Schafer, Lynn (Box 254, Folder 10)
    - Schnell, Susan (Box 254, Folder 11)
    - Scherchen-Hsiao, Ms. Tona (Box 254, Folder 12)
    - Scherperel, Michael (Box 254, Folder 13)
    - Santer, Renee (Box 254, Folder 14)
    - Santwan, Arvind (Box 254, Folder 15)
    - Schidlovsky, Nicholas (Box 254, Folder 16)
    - Schiff, Zina (Box 254, Folder 17)
    - Schmidt, Mr. Gayle (Box 254, Folder 18)
    - Schmidt, Judith (Box 254, Folder 19)
    - Schock, June (Box 254, Folder 20)
    - Schober, Brian (Box 254, Folder 21)
    - Scheidner, Victoria (Box 254, Folder 22)
    - Schober, Brian (Box 254, Folder 23)
    - Schock, June (Box 254, Folder 24)
    - Arnold Schoenberg Institute, University of Southern California (Box 254, Folder 25)
    - Schoenfield, Paul (Box 254, Folder 26)
    - Schonthal, Ruth (Box 254, Folder 27)
    - Schrader, Barry (Box 254, Folder 28)
    - Schubel, Max (Box 254, Folder 29)
    - Schuler, Richard (Box 255, Folder 1)
    - Schulte, Rolf (Box 255, Folder 2)
    - Schuman, Patricia (Box 255, Folder 3)
    - Schuman-Post, Brenda (Box 255, Folder 4)
    - Schmate, Sheila (Box 255, Folder 5)
    - Schwantner, Joseph (Box 255, Folder 6)
    - Schwartz, Elliott (Box 255, Folder 7)
    - Schwartz, Robert (Box 255, Folder 8)
    - Scot-Shepherd, Stephen (Box 255, Folder 9)
    - Scrable, Heidi (Box 255, Folder 10)
    - Sea Cliff Chamber Players, Inc. (Box 255, Folder 11)
    - Seattle Opera Association, Inc. (Box 255, Folder 12)
    - Seelig, Timothy G. (Box 255, Folder 13)
    - Segal, Peter (duo with Janet Ketchum) (Box 255, Folder 14)
    - Segal and Mitchell Duo (Box 255, Folder 15)
    - Sego, Mary Ann (Box 255, Folder 16)
    - Sekon, Josef (Box 255, Folder 17)
    - Seletsky, Harold (Box 255, Folder 18)
    - Selig, Robert (Box 255, Folder 19)
    - Seligman, Robert (Box 256, Folder 1)
    - Sellars, James (Box 256, Folder 2)
    - S. E. M. Ensemble (Box 256, Folder 3)
    - Semegen, Ms. Daria (Box 256, Folder 4)
    - Senator, Ronald Paul (Box 256, Folder 5)
    - Sepe, Christine (Box 256, Folder 6)
    - Sequoia String Quartet (Box 256, Folder 7)
    - Serebrier, Jose (Box 256, Folder 8)
    - Serrano, Carlos (Box 256, Folder 9)
    - Servant, Gregory (Box 256, Folder 10)
    - Shakleford, Rudy (Box 256, Folder 11)
    - Shahid, Jameela G. (Box 256, Folder 12)
    - Shannon, Donald (Box 256, Folder 13)
    - Shapinsky, Ian (Box 256, Folder 14)
    - Shapiro, Michael Jeffrey (Box 256, Folder 15)
    - Sharman, Lynda (Box 256, Folder 16)
    - Sharon, Boaz (Box 256, Folder 17)
    - Sharp, Martha (Box 256, Folder 18)
    - Shattenkirk, Ray (Box 256, Folder 19)
    - Shearer, Mary (Box 256, Folder 20)
    - Shelley, Martha (Box 256, Folder 21)
    - Shenk, Earle (Box 256, Folder 22)
    - Sheppard, C. James (Box 256, Folder 23)
    - Sheppard, Craig (Box 256, Folder 24)
    - Sher, Richard (Box 256, Folder 25)
    - Shere, Charles (Box 257, Folder 1)
    - Sherman, Mark (Box 257, Folder 2)
    - Sherrard, Sharon (Box 257, Folder 3)
    - Shexnayder, Brian (Box 257, Folder 4)
    - Shigeoka, Raymond (Box 257, Folder 5)
    - Shoff, Dean (Box 257, Folder 6)
    - Sholin, Norman (Box 257, Folder 7)
    - Shore, Joseph (Box 257, Folder 8)
    - Shorr, Raoul (Box 257, Folder 9)
    - Shrude, Marilyn (Box 257, Folder 10)
    - Shuman, Mark (Box 257, Folder 11)
    - Siegel, Frank (Box 257, Folder 12)
    - Siegel, Wayne (Box 257, Folder 13)
    - Siegfried, Kathleen (Box 257, Folder 14)
    - Silbert, Gershon (Box 257, Folder 15)
    - Silsbee, Ann (Box 257, Folder 16)
    - Silver, Jacquelyne (Box 257, Folder 17)
    - Silver, Jacquelyne (Box 257, Folder 18)
    - Silverman, Faye-Ellen (Box 257, Folder 19)
    - Simons, David (Box 257, Folder 20)
    - Sims, Ezra (Box 257, Folder 21)
    - Sine Nomine Singers (Box 257, Folder 22)
    - Singer, David (Box 257, Folder 23)
    - Singleton, Alvin (Box 257, Folder 24)
    - Sirota, Victoria (Box 257, Folder 25)
    - Sitterly, James (Box 258, Folder 1)
    - Sklar, Pamela (Box 258, Folder 2)
    - Sloane, Ethan (Box 258, Folder 3)
    - Small, Elisabeth (Box 258, Folder 4)
    - Smalls, Alexander (Box 258, Folder 5)
    - Smart, Cary (Box 258, Folder 6)
    - Smartt, Michael V. (Box 258, Folder 7)
    - Smedvig, Rolf (Box 258, Folder 8)
    - Smeltzer, Susan (Box 258, Folder 9)
    - Smetona, Vrytautas (Box 258, Folder 10)
    - Smith, Alma Jean (Box 258, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Mr. Dale (Box 258, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Greg (Box 258, Folder 13)
    - Smith, Karen H. (Box 258, Folder 14)
    - Smith, Linda (Box 258, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Paul (Box 258, Folder 16)
    - Smith, Spencer (Box 258, Folder 17)
    - Smith, Stephen (Box 258, Folder 18)
    - Smith, Susan (Box 258, Folder 19)
    - Smith, William Lee (Box 258, Folder 20)
    - Smith, William Lidell (Box 258, Folder 21)
    - Smolanoff, Michael (Box 258, Folder 22)
    - Snow, David (Box 258, Folder 23)
    - Soh, Mr. Byung Sun (Box 258, Folder 24)
    - SoHo Baroque Opera Company (Box 258, Folder 25)
    - Sollberger, Harvey (Box 258, Folder 26)
    - Solomon, Joyce (Box 258, Folder 27)
    - Solow, Jeffrey (Box 258, Folder 28)
    - Sonos Chamber Ensemble (Box 258, Folder 29)
    - Sonnenber, Melanie (Box 259, Folder 1)
    - Soundscape Presents (Box 259, Folder 2)
    - South, Pamela (Box 259, Folder 3)
    - South Dakota String Quartet (Box 259, Folder 4)
    - Spacagna, Maria (Box 259, Folder 5)
    - Spangler, Marianne (Box 259, Folder 6)
    - Spann, Annette (Box 259, Folder 7)
    - Sparks, Brian (Box 259, Folder 8)
    - Speculum Musicae, Inc. (Box 259, Folder 9)
    - Spencer, Alton (Box 259, Folder 10)
    - Spiegel, Laurie (Box 259, Folder 11)
    - Spiegel, Victor (Box 259, Folder 12)
    - Spiegelman, Joel (Box 259, Folder 13)
    - Spivack, Joe (Box 259, Folder 14)
    - Sponseller, Jacquelyn (Box 259, Folder 15)
    - Spague, Jonathan (Box 259, Folder 16)
    - Spring Opera Theater (Box 260, Folder 1)
    - Springstead Woodwind Quintet (Box 260, Folder 2)
    - Stallman, Robert (Box 260, Folder 3)
    - Stalvey, Dorrance (Box 260, Folder 4)
    - Stamm, Jeffrey K. (Box 260, Folder 5)
    - Stanley, Helen (Box 260, Folder 6)
    - Stanton, Mary (Box 260, Folder 7)
    - Stanziano, Albert (Box 260, Folder 8)
    - Stapp, Gregory (Box 260, Folder 9)
    - Starin, Stefani (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - Starobin, David (Box 260, Folder 11)
    - Stasis, Patricia (Box 260, Folder 12)
    - Steber (Eleanor) Music Foundation (Box 260, Folder 13)
    - Stein, Louise Kathrin (Box 260, Folder 14)
    - Steiner, Gitta (Box 260, Folder 15)
    - Steiner, Gretchen (Box 260, Folder 16)
    - Steinhaus, Barbara (Box 260, Folder 17)
    - Stephenson, Christine (Box 260, Folder 18)
    - Stephenson, Kathleen (Box 260, Folder 19)
    - Stephenson, Mary Elizabeth (Box 260, Folder 20)
    - Stern, Max (Box 260, Folder 21)
    - Stern, Robert (Box 260, Folder 22)
    - Sternklar, Avraham (Box 260, Folder 23)
    - Stettner, Ellen (Box 260, Folder 24)
    - Stiles, Patricia (Box 261, Folder 1)
    - Stillman, Julia (Box 261, Folder 2)
    - Stock, David (Box 261, Folder 3)
    - Stoeppelmann, Janet (Box 261, Folder 4)
    - Stoering, Donna (Box 261, Folder 5)
    - Stokes, Eric (Box 261, Folder 6)
    - Stomsvik, Diana (Box 261, Folder 7)
    - Stone, Patricia (Box 261, Folder 8)
    - Stone, Sandra (Box 261, Folder 9)
    - Stone, William (Box 261, Folder 10)
    - Stornetta, Catherine (Box 261, Folder 11)
    - Stott, John (Box 261, Folder 12)
    - Stowe, Sandra (Box 261, Folder 13)
    - Strange, Richard (Box 261, Folder 14)
    - Stravinsky Symposium (Box 261, Folder 15)
    - Stawberry Banke, Inc. - Stawberry Banke Chamber Music Festival (Box 261, Folder 16)
    - Strilko, Anthony (Box 261, Folder 17)
    - Strizich, Catherine and Robert (Box 262, Folder 1)
    - Strummer, Peter (Box 262, Folder 2)
    - Strunk, Steven (Box 262, Folder 3)
    - Stucky, Steven (Box 262, Folder 4)
    - Suarez, Antonio (Box 262, Folder 5)
    - Sublette, Ned (Box 262, Folder 6)
    - Such, John (Box 262, Folder 7)
    - Suhrstedt Duo (Box 262, Folder 8)
    - Summer, Joseph (Box 262, Folder 9)
    - Summer Opera Institute, 1980 (Box 262, Folder 10)
    - Summer Opera Theatre Company, Inc., Washington, D.C. (Box 262, Folder 11)
    - Summer, Ann (Box 262, Folder 12)
    - Summers (Elaine) Experimental Intermedia Foundation, Inc. (Box 262, Folder 13)
    - Sumner, Jay (Box 262, Folder 14)
    - Sumrow, Kathie (Box 262, Folder 15)
    - Sundine, Stephanie (Box 262, Folder 16)
    - Sur, Donald (Box 262, Folder 17)
    - Surveys, 1965-1977 (Box 262, Folder 18)
    - Sussman, Stanley (Box 262, Folder 19)
    - Sutliff, Richard (Box 262, Folder 20)
    - Svoboda, Tomas (Box 263, Folder 1)
    - Swedish, Stephen (Box 263, Folder 2)
    - Swack, Irwin (Box 263, Folder 3)
    - Swann, Jeffrey (Box 263, Folder 4)
    - Swansbourne, Clive (Box 263, Folder 5)
    - Swift, John D. (Box 263, Folder 6)
    - Swint, Sheryl (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Sylvano, Bonnie (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Syverud, Stephen (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - Szabo, Burt (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - Szymkowicz, Cynthia (Box 263, Folder 11)
    - Tafelmusik (Box 263, Folder 12)
    - Taft Corporation (Box 263, Folder 13)
    - Tag Foundation, Ltd. (Box 263, Folder 14)
    - Tait, Catherine (Box 263, Folder 15)
    - Talley, Mr. Dana (Box 263, Folder 16)
    - Tan, Margaret Hee-Leng (Box 263, Folder 17)
    - Tannenbaum, David (Box 263, Folder 18)
    - Tannenbaum, Elias (Box 263, Folder 19)
    - Tanner, Jerre E. (Box 263, Folder 20)
    - Taub, Robert (Box 263, Folder 21)
    - Tax Responsibilities - Individual Grantees, 1971-1978 (Box 263, Folder 22)
    - Taylor, Ms. Grier (Box 264, Folder 1)
    - Taylor, Marsha (Box 264, Folder 2)
    - Tcherepnin, Ivan (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Teitelbaum, Richard (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - Telese, Maryanne (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Tenney, James (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Termination of Martha Baird Fund for Music - News Clippings, Letters, 1982 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - Terry, Michael (Box 264, Folder 8)
    - Texas Opera Theater (Box 264, Folder 9)
    - Theatre Chamber Players, Inc. (Box 264, Folder 10)
    - Theatre Development Fund, Inc. (Box 264, Folder 11)
    - Theberge, Paul (Box 264, Folder 12)
    - Theeman, Nancy Sarah (Box 264, Folder 13)
    - Themmen, Ivana (Box 264, Folder 14)
    - Thigpen, Martha (Box 264, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, Andrew (Box 264, Folder 16)
    - Thomas, Carter (Box 264, Folder 17)
    - Thomas, Ronald (Box 264, Folder 18)
    - Thome, Diane (Box 265, Folder 1)
    - Thompson (Helen M.) Project (Box 265, Folder 2)
    - Thomspon, Helen M. (Box 265, Folder 3)
    - Thomson, Jacqueline (Box 265, Folder 4)
    - Thorington, Helen (Box 265, Folder 5)
    - Thorne, Francis (Box 265, Folder 6)
    - Thorngren, Jane (Box 265, Folder 7)
    - Thow, John (Box 265, Folder 8)
    - Threatte, Charles (Box 265, Folder 9)
    - Tigner, David (Box 265, Folder 10)
    - Tinturin, Glenn (Box 265, Folder 11)
    - Tipei, Sever (Box 265, Folder 12)
    - Tobias, Paul (Box 265, Folder 13)
    - Todaro, Joanne (Box 265, Folder 14)
    - Todd, George B. (Box 265, Folder 15)
    - Todd, R. Larry (Box 265, Folder 16)
    - Toensing, Richard (Box 265, Folder 17)
    - Toliver, Z. Edmund (Box 265, Folder 18)
    - Tomasello, Andrew (Box 265, Folder 19)
    - Tomingas, Byron Paul (Box 265, Folder 20)
    - Tomlinson, Gary (Box 265, Folder 21)
    - Tompkins, Fred (Box 265, Folder 22)
    - Toney, Martha (Box 265, Folder 23)
    - Toufexis and Ernst, Duo pianists (Box 265, Folder 24)
    - Tower, Joan (Box 266, Folder 1)
    - Tricomi, Karl (Box 266, Folder 2)
    - Tri-Cities Opera (Box 266, Folder 3)
    - Triestram, David (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - Trilling, Mark (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Troise, Michele (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Trombly, Preston (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Trotti, Nancy P. (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Trout, John (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - Troy, Barbara (Box 266, Folder 9A)
    - Trythall, Richard (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - Tsandoulas, Gerasimos Nicholas (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - Tseitlin, Irina (Box 266, Folder 12)
    - Tsontakis, George (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - Tsopelas, Vinia (Box 266, Folder 14)
    - Tsypin, Vladimir (Box 266, Folder 15)
    - Tudor, Donald (Box 266, Folder 16)
    - Tuggle, James (Box 266, Folder 17)
    - Tull, Dr. Fisher A., Sam Houston State University, Music Department, Huntsville, TX (Box 266, Folder 18)
    - Tumarkin, Robert (Box 266, Folder 19)
    - Turinia, Thomas (Box 266, Folder 20)
    - Turner, William (Box 266, Folder 21)
    - Turok, Paul (Box 266, Folder 22)
    - Turrin, Joseph (Box 266, Folder 23)
    - Twentieth Century Consort (Box 267, Folder 1)
    - Tyeska, James (Box 267, Folder 2)
    - Tyson, John (Box 267, Folder 3)
    - Udovich, JoAnn (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - Udow, Michael (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - Ultan, Lloyd (Box 267, Folder 6)
    - Ung, Chinary (Box 267, Folder 7)
    - Ungar, Tamas (Box 267, Folder 8)
    - U. S. Tax Reform Act 1969 - General Information, 1968-1974 (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - United States Tax Reform Act 1969 - Recipients of Fund Contributions (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - University of Chicago - Verdi Edition (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - University Composers Exchange, 1978-1982 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - University of Illinois - Resources of American Music History (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - Uris, Dorothy (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - Utah Opera Company (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - Van Appledorn, Mary Jeanne (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Vance, Nancy (Box 268, Folder 7)
    - Van Cleve, Sandra Fink (Box 268, Folder 8)
    - Vandekieft, Kathleen (Box 268, Folder 9)
    - Van Derick, Peter (Box 268, Folder 10)
    - Van De Vate, Nancy (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Vaness, Carol (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - Van Hecke, Holly (Box 268, Folder 13)
    - Van Ingen, Elizabeth (Box 268, Folder 14)
    - Van Lidth De Jeude, C. Philip J. (Box 268, Folder 15)
    - Van Nostrand, Burr (Box 268, Folder 16)
    - Van Valkenburg, Robert (Box 268, Folder 17)
    - Van Wyke, Sherrie (Box 268, Folder 18)
    - Van Zabner, Antoinette (Box 268, Folder 19)
    - Vargas, Milagro (Box 268, Folder 20)
    - Vaughan, Edward (Box 268, Folder 21)
    - Vaughn, Beverly (Box 268, Folder 22)
    - Vehar, Persis (Box 268, Folder 23)
    - Veloze, Alise (Box 268, Folder 24)
    - Velta, Lee (Box 268, Folder 25)
    - Vercoe, Elizabeth (Box 268, Folder 26)
    - Vernon, Jane (Box 268, Folder 27)
    - Vigeland, Nils (Box 268, Folder 28)
    - Vignare, Gary (Box 268, Folder 29)
    - Villa, Joseph (Box 268, Folder 30)
    - Villarini, Awilda (Box 268, Folder 31)
    - Vinograde, Peter (Box 268, Folder 32)
    - Violin Makers (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Opera Association, Inc. (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Vogel, Jo-Ellen (Jodi) (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Voices of Change (Box 269, Folder 4)
    - Vollinger, William (Box 269, Folder 5)
    - Voloshin, Metro John (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Vondra, Marilyn (Box 269, Folder 7)
    - Voogt, Ronald (Box 269, Folder 8)
    - Vote, Franz (Box 269, Folder 9)
  - W-X-Y-Z
    - Wade, Mr. Dell G. (Box 269, Folder 10)
    - Wadsworth, Charles (Box 269, Folder 11)
    - Wadsworth, Charles (Box 269, Folder 12)
    - Wagner, James (Box 269, Folder 13)
    - Wagner, Lauren (Box 269, Folder 14)
    - Wain, Roberta (Box 269, Folder 15)
    - Wakefield, Mary (Box 269, Folder 16)
    - Walant, Glen (Box 269, Folder 17)
    - Waldman, Mara (Box 269, Folder 18)
    - Walker Art Center, Inc. (Box 269, Folder 19)
    - Walker, Charles John (Box 269, Folder 20)
    - Walker, Diane (Box 270, Folder 1)
    - Walker, Ernestine (Box 270, Folder 2)
    - Walker, Linda (Box 270, Folder 3)
    - Walker, Miss Nelsie (Box 270, Folder 4)
    - Walker, Paul Mark (Box 270, Folder 5)
    - Walker, Sandra (Box 270, Folder 6)
    - Wallace, Mr. Robin (Box 270, Folder 7)
    - Wallach, Joelle (Box 270, Folder 8)
    - Wallstein, Mr. Terry (Box 270, Folder 9)
    - Wall Street Chamber Players (Box 270, Folder 10)
    - Walsh, Diane (Box 270, Folder 11)
    - Walters, Anne Elizabeth (Box 270, Folder 12)
    - Walters, Raymond (Box 270, Folder 13)
    - Ward, Robert (Box 270, Folder 14)
    - Ward, Wesley A. (Box 270, Folder 15)
    - Ward-Steinman, David (Box 270, Folder 16)
    - Ware, John (Box 270, Folder 17)
    - Warmington, Flynn (Box 270, Folder 18)
    - Warner, Joseph (Box 270, Folder 19)
    - Warren, Arthur (Box 270, Folder 20)
    - Washburn, Gary (Box 270, Folder 21)
    - Washington, Fred (Box 270, Folder 22)
    - Washington Opera (Box 270, Folder 23)
    - Waterman, Ruth (Box 271, Folder 1)
    - Waters, Greg (Box 271, Folder 2)
    - Watkins, David (Box 271, Folder 3)
    - Watkins, Sara (Box 271, Folder 4)
    - Watts, John (Box 271, Folder 5)
    - The Waverly Consort (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - The Waverly Consort (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - Webster, Michael (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - Weidenaar, Reynold (Box 271, Folder 9)
    - Weigl, Vally (Box 271, Folder 10)
    - Weiner, Rickie (Box 271, Folder 11)
    - Weinfeld, Christine (Box 272, Folder 1)
    - Weisberg, Arthur (Box 272, Folder 2)
    - Weiss, Elizabeth (Box 272, Folder 3)
    - Weiss, Mark (Box 272, Folder 4)
    - Welborn, Ms. Jan (Box 272, Folder 5)
    - Welcher, Louis (Box 272, Folder 6)
    - Weller, Ira (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - Wellman, Donna (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - Wells, Barbara (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - Wells, Jeffrey (Box 272, Folder 10)
    - Wentworth, Pamela (Box 272, Folder 11)
    - Wentzel, Andrew (Box 272, Folder 12)
    - Wernick, Richard (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - West, Stephen (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1974-1982 (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1980-1981 (Box 272, Folder 16)
    - West Coast Auditions, 1980-1981 (Box 272, Folder 17)
    - Westcott, Mark (Box 272, Folder 18)
    - Western Opera Theatre, Inc. (Box 272, Folder 19)
    - The Western Wind (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - Westfall, David (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Westney, William (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Wetzler, Holly (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Wexler, Mathias (Box 273, Folder 5)
    - WGN Continental Broadcasting (Box 273, Folder 6)
    - Wheeler, Ms. Kimball (Box 273, Folder 7)
    - Wheeler, Lawrence (Box 273, Folder 8)
    - White, Gary (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - White, John Paul (Box 273, Folder 10)
    - White, Wendy (Box 273, Folder 11)
    - WHYY-TV, Philadelphia (Box 273, Folder 12)
    - Wickenden, Lynne (Box 273, Folder 13)
    - Widdoes, Lawrence (Box 273, Folder 14)
    - Wiens, Frank (Box 273, Folder 15)
    - Wilcken, Lois (Box 273, Folder 16)
    - Wilcox, Thomas (Box 273, Folder 17)
    - Wilkinson, Barbara (Box 273, Folder 18)
    - Wilkinson, Jane (Box 273, Folder 19)
    - Willard, Lee (Box 273, Folder 20)
    - Willenborg, Patricia (Box 273, Folder 21)
    - Willey, James (Box 273, Folder 22)
    - Williams, Jack Eric (Box 273, Folder 23)
    - Williamson, Marshall (Box 274, Folder 1)
    - Willis, Diane (Box 274, Folder 2)
    - Wilms, Peggy (Box 274, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Antonia Joy (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Wilson, Donald (Box 274, Folder 5)
    - Wilson, John (Box 274, Folder 6)
    - Wilson, Mark Edwards (Box 274, Folder 7)
    - Wilson, Oily (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Wilson, Ransom (Box 274, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Richard (Box 274, Folder 10)
    - Wincenc, Carol (Box 274, Folder 11)
    - Winkler, David (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - Winkler, Kathleen (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - Winkler, Peter (Box 274, Folder 14)